AAA Audio Recording 6145 AV
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
AAA Audio Recording
1971
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
American Arbitration Association (AAA)
6145 AV
1.22 cubic feet
1.2 linear ft.
Audiovisual materials.
5819032
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, March 21, 2013
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, August 19, 2015
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5004: AAA Arbitration in Government 5119: AAA Voluntary Labor Arbitration Tribunal Case Files 6309: AAA Arbitration in the Schools Records
Altieri, James V.; Bailer, Lloyd H.; Barrett, Gerald A., 1912-1990; Dash, G. Allan; Jones, E.A. (Edgar Allan), 1921-; Linn, John Phillip; Middlekauff, Robert M.; Myers, Morris L.; Roberts, Thomas T.; Schmertz, Eric J.; Unterberger, S. Herbert, 1913-1979; Wolf, Benjamin H., b. 1909; American Arbitration Association
5819032
- Linn, John Phillip, 1971; 1 (Box 1)
  Scope and Contents
  Technical issues in labor arbitration: job evaluation, job classification and incentive pay. New York, American Arbitration Association, 1971 -- Master Tape -- (1 of 2)
- Linn, John Phillip, 1971; 2 (Box 1)
  Technical issues in labor arbitration: job evaluation, job classification and incentive pay. New York, American Arbitration Association, 1971 -- Master Tape -- (2 of 2)
- Unterberger, S. Herbert, 1971; 3 (Box 1)
  Arbitration of job evaluation cases. New York, American Arbitration Association, 1971 -- Master Tape
- Unterberger, S. Herbert, 1971; 4 (Box 1)
  Arbitration of wage incentive cases. New York, American Arbitration Association, 1971 -- Master Tape
- Altieri, James V., 1971; 5 (Box 1)
  Arbitrability. New York, American Arbitration Association, 1971 -- Master Tape
- Warns, Carl A., 1971; 6 (Box 1)
- Myers, Morris L. // Wolf, Benjamin H., 1971; 7 (Box 1)
  Arbitrability. // management rights. - New York, American Arbitration Association, 1971 -- Master Tape
- Jones, Edgar Allan Jr., 1971; 8 (Box 1)
  Management rights. New York, American Arbitration Association, 1971 -- Master Tape
- Bailer, Lloyd H., 1971; 9 (Box 1)
  Seniority and ability. New York, American Arbitration Association, 1971 -- Master Tape
- Schmertz, Eric J. // Barrett, Gerald A., 1971; 10 (Box 1)
  Seniority and ability. - New York, American Arbitration Association, 1971 -- Master Tape
- Middlekauff, Robert m.; Edwards, Nelson Jack; Wallen, Saul, 1971; 11 (Box 1)
  Three viewpoints on employing the disadvantaged. - New York, American Arbitration Association, 1971 -- (1 of 2)
- Middlekauf, Robert M.; Edwards, Nelson Jack; Wallen, Saul, 1971; 12 (Box 1)
  Three viewpoints on employing the disadvantaged. - New York, American Arbitration Association, 1971 -- Master Tape -- (2 of 2)
- Dash, G. Allan Jr. // Abernethy, Byron R., 1971; 13 (Box 1)
  Discipline and discharge -- New York, American Arbitration Association, 1971 -- Master Tape
- Wildebush, Joseph F., 1971; 14 (Box 1)
  Discipline and discharge. New York, American Arbitration Association, 1971 -- Master Tape
- Roberts, Thomas T., 1971; 15 (Box 1)
- Discipline and discharge / Thomas T. Roberts, 1 (Box 2)
- Employing the Disadvantage: Three Viewpoints / Robert M. Middlekauff, Nelson Jack Edwards, Saul Wallen, 1 (Box 3)